https://www.brianstoys.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
Star WarsModernAction Figures3.75 inch Action Figures6 inch Action Figures12 inch Action FiguresMulti-Figure PacksOtherAccessoriesBeastExclusiveLife-SizeMiscellaneousPrototypesMicro MachinesCollector PlatesBobbleheadsPlaysetsVehiclesThe Force AwakensRogue One: A Star Wars Story40th AnniversarySolo: A Star Wars StoryThe Last JediSaleVintageAction Figures4 inch Figures12 inch-FiguresAccessoriesBeastCoinsDie-CastFigure CasesMicro CollectionsMiscellaneousProduct PhotosStore DisplaysDon PostPlush DollsSigmaHamilton PlatesPuzzlesPlaysetsPrototypesVehiclesAFA GradedCollectiblesValentines Day 2019 Up to 60% OffStatuesFX LightsabersBustsProp ReplicasLicensed ArtworkMaquettesMiscellaneousNew ListingsPrincess LeiaChristmas 2017PreordersHalloween 2018Black Friday Up To 70% Off 201825% Off Select The Force Awakens, Rogue One, 40th Anniversary & The Last Jedi
Other CollectiblesMarvelAction FiguresMarvel LegendsExclusivesReplicasTransformersMasters of the UniverseIndiana JonesSecret WarsThundercatsVideo GamesSuppliesConstruction SetsOtherAction FiguresAccessoriesVehiclesMiscellaneousBrand New Vintage AFANew ACME Archives Star Wars Artwork
Account
Vintage
4-inch Figures
12-inch Figures
Vehicles
Accessories
Playsets
AFA Graded
Puzzles
Looking for specials?:
See Vintage Sales
Modern
3.75-inch Figures
6-inch Figures
12-inch Figures
Multi-Figure Packs
Vehicles
Playsets
Bobbleheads
Looking for specials?:
See Modern Sales
Collectibles
Statues
FX Lightsabers
Busts
Prop Replicas
Licensed Artwork
Maquettes
Miscellaneous
Other collections:
G.I.Joe
Transformers
Masters of the Universe
Video Games
Other Collections
Marvel
Transformers
G.I.Joe
Other
Other collections:
G.I.Joe
Transformers
Masters of the Universe
Video Games
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting Brianstoys.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If we link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.Collection of InformationWe collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request.Cookie/Tracking TechnologyThe Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.Distribution of InformationWe may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.Commitment to Data SecurityYour personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.Privacy Contact informationIf you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:* By E-Mail: sales@brianstoys.com* By Phone: (608) 687-7572We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
